Guide to the George Washington University Publications collection, 1924-2017 RG0154
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Population Studies, Series 15
  - Buzzard Point Planning Study: Completing the Vision, January 1971; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Downtown Afoot: Paving the Way for Pedestrians, July 1981; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Accuracy Analysis for Projections of Manpower in Metropolitan Areas, 1967; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The George Washington University Directory of Consulting Firms, 1979; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The George Washington University Directory of Consulting Firms, 1979; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Current Financial Prospects for the District of Columbia: An Uncertain Outlook, March 1983; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Arts in Metropolitan Washington: Some Preliminary Data on Economics, Financing, and Organization, December 1975; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Nonprofit Sector: The Heart of Greater Washington; Assessing the Impact of the District's Fiscal Crisis, July 1995; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Competition Comes to Town: Financial Serviews in the Washington Economy, January 1985; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The George Washington University Directory of Consulting Firms, 1979; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The District of Columbia's Changing Economy and its Future Growth Opportunities, September 1987; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Changing Washington Economy, March 1985; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alternative Service Delivery Approaches Involving Increased Use of the Private Sector, June 1983; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Federal Purchases in the Washington Metropolitan Area, November 1984; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Technology-oriented Firms in the Washington Area, November 1984; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Washington: Leader in Changing Lifestyles, November 1982; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Prevention of Prematurity: A Strategy to Reduce Infant Mortality in the District of Columbia, November 1982; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Sorting-Out of Washingtonians: Patterns of Residential Movement in the Metropolitan Area, May 1980; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Changing Residential Patterns of Racial Minorities in Metropolitan Washington, 1970-1980, June 1982; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Changing Demographic Trends in Inside-beltway Suburbs and the District of Columbia, April 1982; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Greater Washington Data Book: Eighth Edition, 1996; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Greater Washington 1991 Data Book, August 1991; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Shape of the Future: Greater Washington's Population Now to the Year 2000, April 1990; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Greater Washington 1988 Data Book, April 1988; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Greater Washington 1985 Data Book, December 1985; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Greater Washington 1984 Data Book, June 1984; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Washingtonians of Today, June 1980; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Population Problems in Mexico and Central America, 1959; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Caribbean: Population and Resources, 1960; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Population Growth and the Development of South America, 1959; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Population, Manpower, and Economic Development of Eastern Europe, 1961; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Population Growth and Social Change in the Middle East, 1964; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Population Trends and Economic Development in the Far East, 1965; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Population Problems in the Development of India and Southcentral Asia, 1961; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Population Factors in the Development of North Africa, 1960; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Population Pressures in Africa South of the Sahara, 1958; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Control of World Population Growth, 1963; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Population Growth and International Migration, 1962; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - World Population Pressures, 1958; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Population Dilemma: Participants' Edition, 1963; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - American Assembly Report on the Population Dilemma, 1963; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for the Establishment of an International Center for Population Dynamics, September 26, 1975; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Population Information Program: Worldwide Impact System, 1977-1978; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Course ME 251-252 Project A: Transportation in Arlington County, VA (Vol. 1), 1971; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Course ME 251-252 Project B: Dulles Airport Rapid Transit Study, 1973; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Simple State-dependent Gap Acceptance, April 20, 1973; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - On Platoon Formation on Two-Lane Roads, May 20, 1977; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - The Average Speed of a Fast Vehicle Moving in a Stream of Slow Vehicles, June 16, 1978; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Transit Study, Far Southeast: Summary Report, December 1972; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Revitalization of Small Communities: Transportation Options (Vol. 1), July 1973; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Revitalization of Small Communities: Transportation Options (Vol. 2), July 1973; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A Changing Social Institution in an Urban Environment: A Study of the Changing Behavior Patterns of the Disciples of Christ in Los Angeles, 1931; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Traffic Safety Law System, January 3, 1975; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Youth Programs Information and Referral Manual: Second Edition, 1973; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Evaluation of the Operating Efficiencies of the Naitonal Criminal Justice Reference Services (NCJRS), March 31, 1975; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - National Transport Policy Conference, December 1960; Series 15 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- American Studies, Series 16
  - American Studies International Newsletter, 1983-1986; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Studies International Newsletter, 1987-1996; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 25, No. 1), 1987; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 26, No. 1), 1988; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 27, No. 1), 1989; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 28, No. 1), 1990; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 30, No. 1), 1992; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 31, No. 1), 1993; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 32, No. 1), 1994; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 37, Nos. 1-3), 1999; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 38, Nos. 1-3), 2000; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 39, Nos. 1-3), 2001; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 40, Nos. 1-3), 2002; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Studies International (Vol. 41, Nos. 1-2), 2003-02; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Journal of Northeast Asian Studies (Vol. 13, Nos. 2-3), 1994; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Journal of Northeast Asian Studies (Vol. 15, Nos. 2-3), 1996; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Academic Journals for the Study of American Society and Culture, December 1977; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Policy Perspectives: The George Washington University Journal of Public Administration (Vol. 1, No. 1), Spring 1994; Series 16 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Studies on Childhood and Adolescence, Series 17
  - The Status of Research in Children's Television, January 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Review of the Present Status and Future Research Needs of Programs to Develop Parenting Skills, April 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Ecology of Child Development: Research Issues, December 1976; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the Symposium on Ecological Approaches to Research on Child Development, September 1979; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Parenting Skills: Comparability Study, January 1975; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of the Conference on Family Research: Sponsored by the Interagency Panel on Early Childhood Research and Development, September 1974; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Early Childhood Research and Development Needs and Gaps in Federallly Funded Intervention Studies within a Longitudinal Framework, March 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Preliminary Report on the Present Status and Future Needs in Longitudinal Studies in Early Childhood Research and Development, January 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Interagency Research Information System: A Computerized Information System on Federally Sponsored Research, Development, Demonstration, and Evaluation Projects for Children and Youth, June 1976; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Classification of Federally-funded Research in Early Childhood and Adolescence, June 1975; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A Statement and Working Paper on Longitudinal/Intervention Research, April 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Frequency and Quality of Measures Utilized in Federally-sponsored Research on Children and Adolescents, Spring 1976; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - An Analysis of The Process of Establishing and Utilizing Research Priorities, December 1971; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Broad Agency Goals and Agency Research Objectivies for FY 12, December 1971; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Early Childhood and Recommendations for the Future, October 1971; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Early Childhood and Recommendations for the Future (Second Annual Report), November 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Early Childhood and Recommendations for the Future (Third Annual Report), December 1973; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of FY'74 Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Early Childhood and Recommendations for the Future (Third Annual Report), December 1974; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: FY'75 Federal Research and Development Activities Pertaining to Early Childhood (Fifth Annual Report), December 1975; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Preschool and Postscript: An Evaluation of an Inner-City Program, Undated; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - A Review of the Present Status and Future Needs in Day Care Research, November 1971; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Raising America's Children: How Should We Care, 1988; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Day Care: The Role of Washington-Area Local Governments, July 1982; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Group Infant Care Programs: A Survey, Undated; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - When Parents are at Work: A Three-Company Survey of How Employed Parents Arrange Child Care, December 1982; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A Study of Public Communication Critical to Child Health Care: Final Report, August 1972; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect: A Report on the Status of the Research, May 1974; Series 17 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Foster Care in Five States: A Synthesis and Analysis of Studies from Arizona, California, Iowa, Massachusetts, and Vermont, June 1976; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation of the Effectiveness of Illustrated Print Media (Nonverbal) on Family Planning Among Colombians, July 19, 1974; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Teenage Pregnancy and Family Impact, June 1979; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Adolescent Sexuality and the Impact of Teenage Pregnancy from a Black Perspective, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Adolescent Parent Programs and Family Involvement, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Family's Role in Adolescent Sexual Behavior, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Burdens and Benefits: The Impact of Early Childbearing on the Family, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Teenage Women in the USA: Sex, Contraception, Pregnancy, Fertility, and Maternal and Infant Health, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Adolescent Pregnancy: The Impact on Hispanic Adolescents and Their Families, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Government Policies Related to Teenage Family Formation and Functioning: An Inventory, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sex Education and the Prevention of Teenage Pregnancy: An Overview of Policies and Programs in the United States, Undated; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - An Overview of Federal Efforts in Research and Development in th Area of Adolescence, April 1974; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Adolescence Theories and Federal Career Education Programs: Needs and Gaps in Research, September 1974; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - A Generalized Matrix for Research in Youth Participation, January 1977; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Adolesence Research Opinion and National Youth Policy: What We Know and What We Don't Know, Fall 1976; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Transition to Adulthood: Subjects of Research and Development Interest to the Federal Government with Respect to Youth, Spring 1975; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Adolescence (First Annual Report), December 1973; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: An Overview of FY' 74 Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Adolescence (Second Annual Report), December 1974; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: FY' 75 Federal Research and Development Activities Relating to Adolescence (Third Annual Report), December 1975; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Toward Interagency Coordination: FY' 77 Federal Research and Development on Adolescence (Fifth Annual Report), May 1978; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Judges Look at Themselves: A New Approach to Judicial Education, June 1963; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Judges Look at Themselves: Profile of the Nation's Juvenile Court Judges, May 1965; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Judges Look at Themselves: Socialization Principles and Work Styles of the Juvenile Court, August 1965; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Evaluation of the Contribution of Special Programs in the Washington, D.C., Schools to the Prediction and Prevention of Deliquency, 1966; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Evaluation of the Contribution of Special Programs in the Washington, D.C., Schools to the Prediction and Prevention of Deliquency: Final Report, August 1966; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Interim Report of the Family Impact Seminar, April 1978; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Family Impact Seminar: An Introduction, 1977; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Toward an Inventory of Federal Programs with Direct Impact on Families, February 1978; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Toward Comparability in Family Research: An Analysis of Comparability Potential and Information on OCD Research Projects on the Family, November 1974; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Family: Research Considerations and Concerns (A Statement of the Interagency Panel on Early Childhood Research and Development), August 1973; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Study on Formal Representation of Casual Behavioral Relationships, July 31, 1971; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Towards More Comparability and Generalizability of Developmental Research, 1966; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Research Methods in Psychology: Preliminary Edition, 1950; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Elliott School of International Affairs, Series 18
  - The Implications for Arms Control and Disarmament of the United States Exchanges Program with the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe (Vol. II: Appendices), September 1967; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - International Relations: The Study of Foreign Affairs in the Nation's Capital, 1953; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Engaging the World: The Study of International Affairs at The George Washington University, Undated; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - America's Peace Opportunity in the Middle East, 1975; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Humanitarian Military Opperations in the Promotion of World Peace, March 1973; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A World of One Mind, 1972; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Promotion of Peace Among Nations, 1967; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Forecasting in International Relations, June 1970; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A Symposium on the Law of Latin America, 1959; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Trends in Western European Political and Economic Policies, 1969-1985 and Implications for U.S. Security and Strategy (Third Quarterly Report), 1970; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Unification of Europe, January 1953; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The United States and Eastern Europe, May 1968; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Conflict and Consenus in Eastern Europe: Changing Social and Political Attitudes, 1971; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Socialist Theory of International Law, January 1964; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Analysis of the USSR's 24th Party Congress and 9th Five-Year Plan, 1971; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Hasassah Marcus Dossier: A Case History and Petition on Zionist Abdication from the Legacy of the Founding Fathers, June 1970; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Studies in the Law of the Far East and Southeast Asia, 1956; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The United States, the Soviet Union, and Africa: A Conference Organized by The Institute for Sino-Soviet Studies, March 1979; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Workshop on Law as Related to Ocean Development Problems: Workshop Materials, April 20, 1968; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arms Transfers in a Turbulent World, 1988; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Geopolitics and Antarctica, 1990; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Wang, Tsun-Ming, Anti-Communist: An Autobiographical Account of Chinese Communist Thought Reform, November 1954; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dictionary of Terms in Public International Law (Vol. 1), 1948; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dictionary of Terms in Public International Law (Vol. 2), 1948; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dictionary of Terms in Public International Law (Vol. 3), 1948; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dictionary of Terms in Public International Law (Vol. 4), 1948; Series 18 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - International Affairs Review (IAR), 1993-2017; Series 18 (Box 2, Folder 1-9)
    The International Affairs Review is a not-for-profit academic journal published in the Fall and Spring. It is an independently-run publication sponsored by the Elliott School of International Affairs and GW. IAR is still being published and is available online at: https://www.iar-gwu.org/.
- Law School Curricula and Manuals, Series 19
  - Cases in Monetary Law, January 1951; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Copyright Law for Unpublished Manuscripts and Archival Collections, 1992; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Law of Software: 1968 Proceedings, Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Paralegal Training Materials on Legal Problems of the Elderly (Vol. 2), August 27, 1976; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Paralegal Training for Seniors Manual: Legal Research and Writing, 1978; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Paralegal Training for Seniors Manual: Housing, 1978; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Paralegal Training for Seniors Manual: Tax Relief, 1978; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Paralegal Training for Seniors Manual: Principles of Administrative Law, 1978; Series 19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General, Series 20
  - Public Administration, 1939-59-79, 1961; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Paralegal Training for Seniors Manual: Principles of Administrative Law, 1978; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Planning, Programming, and Budgeting: A Technique for Federal Program Planning and Decision-making, November 24, 1965; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Essential Records for Individual Identification and Re-establishment of Individual Rights, September 1962; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Records Essential for Identification of Persons, 1961-1962; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The George Washington University American Assembly Report on The Congress and America's Future, May 1965; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Rise of Competitive Federalism: A New Balance in the Intergovernmental System, 1989; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Effects of Tax Reform on Budget, Tax, and Social Policymaking, 1988; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Content, Controversy, and Control in Antitrust Enforcement, 1987; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blacks in the Westward Movement, 1975; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - A Bibliography of Readings: Fourth Annual Seminar Conference on Hispanic American Affairs at The George Washington University, 1935; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Prehistory of the Arctic Slope of Alaska: Pleistocene Cultural Relationships Between Eurasia and North America, May 28, 1970; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Congressional Debate on the Social Sciences in 1968, December 1968; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The George Washington University Peace Corps Training Program: Nepal, 1962; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Queerly Visible: The Work of JEB (Joan E. Biren), 1971-1991, 1997; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - An Introduction to Statistics for the Social Scientist, Undated; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Readings for Introductory Economics: National Income, Savings, and Investment, Undated; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Human Factors in Civic Action: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, June 1963; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Research Memorandum: A Selected Bibliography of Cross-Cultural Change Projects, October 1964; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Examples of Cross-Cultural Problems Encountered by Americans Working Overseas: An Instructor's Handbook, May 1965; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Our Stories, Our Solutions: Building a Learning Community Through Cases, 1993; Series 20 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GW-Wide publications, 1947-2013; Series 20 (Box 2)
    Folders relate to a number of GW programs including GW magazine, departmental publicatons, Washington DC, publications about events, endowment reports, financial reports, planned giving, and President's Report.
  - Winter convocation - 125th year, 1941 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The productivity of federally financed research and development, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Locating global research and development, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lab medicine class notes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The birth of a medical specialty - William Z. Fradkin, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    The author was the first to introduce diarrheal diseases as a fulltime subspecialty of gastroenterology.
- Science and Biology, Series 21
  - An Interactive Computer System for Multicriteria Faculty Location, February 29, 1980; Series 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Software Engineering Efforts for Style-Independent Interactive Systems, April 1982; Series 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Brief Description on Man-computer Dynamic Scheduling Systems, October 31, 1972; Series 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Some Results on Generalized Connectivity with Applications to Topological Design of Fault-tolerant Multicomputers, April 1971; Series 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)